http://www.onecle.com/info/privacy.shtml

Home: Privacy Policy
OneCLE is committed to protecting the privacy and security of all individuals who use our site. Our goal is to provide an Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, from time to time we may collect information during your visits. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you learn more about the personal information we collect, who we might share it with, and how we protect it.
Note: Additional terms and conditions, if any, regarding the collection and use of your information may also be provided to you before you sign up for a particular OneCLE service - privacy policies for those services will be linked from those particular areas or sections of our site.
What Information Do We Collect?
OneCLE collects personal information in three ways - through information provided directly from our users, from information collected through web server logs and through cookies.
Information Supplied by Our Users
OneCLE collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, and telephone number. OneCLE may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, and legal interests. OneCLE does not collect any of this unique information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.
Additionally, if you send us a cease and desist notice, letter or e-mail asking us to remove one of the contracts we retrieved from a public domain securities filing, your e-mail or letter to us may be forwarded in its entirety to the Chilling Effects Clearinghouse.
At their discretion, they may publicly display such cease and desist notice, letter or e-mail on their web site.
We may also reproduce all or portions of the cease and desist notice, letter or e-mail on our own website.
Information from Web Server Logs
OneCLE records and saves information about you from our web server logs such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the time day you visited and your browser type. This information is used to verify our records and to provide better services to you.
Information from Cookies
In order to offer and provide you with personalized services, OneCLE may use “cookies” to store and help track your information. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. OneCLE will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.
Note: Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies. You should be aware though that some parts of the OneCLE Web site and services may not function properly if you refuse cookies.
Links to Other Sites
OneCLE encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to visit
from OneCLE so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. OneCLE is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the OneCLE site.
Use or Disclosure of your Personal Information to Third Parties and Co-Brand Partners
OneCLE will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission. OneCLE may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on OneCLE, protect and defend the rights or property of OneCLE or act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of OneCLE or members of the public. If you participate in any MCLE activity on the OneCLE Web site, OneCLE may disclose your personal information listed in the official record of attendance to the State Bar upon their request.
Onecle utilizes certain services from Google for ad serving and web traffic analysis.
Please review Google's privacy policy for more information on how Google AdSense and Google Analytics stores your personal information.
These Google servies may place and read cookies on your browser, or use web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on the OneCLE website.
Additionally, Google uses the DART cookie to enables it to serve ads to based on your visits to OneCLE and other sites on the Internet.
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Certain OneCLE services and content may be co-branded with another company.
If you register for or use such services, both OneCLE and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services.
In such cases, either a joint privacy statement or a link to the other company's privacy statement will be provided, which will provide you with information about how the other company will use the information and how you can contact the other company with requests to access the information or other inquiries.
If you send us a cease and desist notice, letter or e-mail asking us to remove one of the contracts we retrieved from a public domain securities filing, your e-mail or letter to us may be forwarded in its entirety to the Chilling Effects Clearinghouse.
At their discretion, they may publicly display such cease and desist notice, letter or e-mail on their web site.
We may also reproduce all or portions of the cease and desist notice, letter or e-mail on our own website.
Protecting Your Information
While OneCLE is committed to protecting your personal information, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords you set up and/or any account information.
Correcting Inaccuracies
When you sign up for OneCLE's products and service, we may send you an e-mail confirming your new account. The message will be sent to the address that you supplied to us at the time of sign-up and will describe ways for you to change or delete the account information provided. Remember to keep the confirmation e-mail as it will also contain information that will help you in case you run into problems accessing our services.
We welcome your comments or questions.
